Guide to the Advisory Committee on the Status of Women records, 1970-2006.
Advisory Committee on the Status of Women records, 1970-2006
- Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, and Related Materials
  - Events - Women’s Studies conference “Women and Gender Relations in Germany & East Europe”, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Employee Day, photo of ACSW and PCCW members, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Women Faculty Reception, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Panel Discussion on Cornell’s Progress Towards Diversity Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Peer Educators in Human Relations Spring Connection Series, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Personal Safety Brown Bag Lunch: Blue Lights, Personal Alarms and Assault response, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Lee Moon: Burnout, Prevention and Recovery, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Susan Bianchi‐Sand: “Pay Equity for Women”, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Panel Discussion on “Women and Tenure at Cornell: Choices, Strategies and Tactics”, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Sharon Dittman: Women and AIDS, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Take our Children to Work Day, Human Resource Services, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cook Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Notes for Meeting with President Rhodes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Re: Second Year of Mentoring Pilot Program, seeking participation, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Women in Leadership Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cook Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Summary of Accomplishments, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Mentoring Subcommittee, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Women’s Center, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Women Advocating for University Improvement (WAUI), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Women in Leadership Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Cook Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report - Educational and Awareness Events, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Susan Murphy Re: In appreciation of Effective Leadership and Concern for Students, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Publicity - “Educating, Advocating & Building Bridges,” ACSW article in The Cornell Workplace ACSW Pamphlet, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cook Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Membership Applications - Re: Affirmation of Judy Hart’s Lifelong Membership, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Re: Cornell Health Insurance does not cover Birth Control pills, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - ACSW article for Pawprint, Women’s History Month, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Re: Seeking support for University Mentoring Program, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Events - Employee Assembly: Project 2000 Open Forum (downsizing support staff), 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Events - Fifth Annual Cook Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Events - ACSW Retreat, June 12, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Members and Former Members, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Winnie Taylor Re: Survey to assess why women leave Cornell, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gender Research - “Cornell Mourns Passing of Prominent Feminist” Alice Cook Article, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gender Research - Davidson, John. “The Tenure Trap.” Working Woman, June 1997. p 36‐41., 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Events - ACSW Holiday Party, 1997-12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Events - Cook Awards, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Members, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - PCCW Grant Information, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Members and Former Members, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Women’s Resource Center Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Members, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Membership Applications, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Website Launch, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Members, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and Membership Applications, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Members, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ACSW Brochure, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jennie Farley Obituary, 2002-06-19 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, Orientation Packet includes description and history of ACSW, 2003-09-2003-11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Annual Checklist for ACSW activities, 2003-09-2003-11 (Box 2, Folder 13)